COMPATRIOOTAAAAA!
Now if you listen to me eh :,(
Now if you make me
case eh
Look like
by eye :v
served
per tooth :vvvv
GOODBYE
Very good little creatures of the Lord
how are you?
Ehhh
It's 7 in the morning
or something like that
I have no fucking idea
What time is it, okay?
but...
We are on our way to Mexico
This is going to be very brief, okay.
hey
because this...
the taxi waiting for me downstairs
so
I'm going to say goodbye now
of the kittens
Wilson
Aaaa thank you
Man, I really feel sorry for always abandoning them.
for so long, the truth
My mother will take care of them, eh?
Mom, please take care of them.
Scratching you, I also say goodbye
But you already know what this is about, right, Zhi?
Ehhh, well, we're going to leave now and...
*Suspiros* NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO
*La maldita flauta*
I had forgotten that Bonsai Dopoulos was dead.
In Peru I will find a cure for you, don't worry.
*Op music*
We just arrived in Peru, in Lima andyyyyyyyyy it's playing. It looks like Silent Hill (?)
Look, this is our first time in Peru, so we don't know what it's going to be like...
Man
Manhe, in our fucking life we've been to Peru
What do you mean, not an idiot?
If we were in Peru last year, don't you remember?
He was, he's messing with me, the moron is messing with me.
We don't know how people will be here.
Ceviche
Okay, here we are with the security guard, he has confirmed to us
that there are people outside but it is fenced
They're not going to kill us... Today, we won't die
"Not today" *Laughs*
GODDAMN
They've seen you, huh, I think.
It sticks its head out
*Shouting*
This camera records :v
Mother Mother Mother
(Lots of screaming, but something about a photo xdxd)
LOL
Damn, that's right, man... That's right
I'm still like...
I have my clothes intact, my hair...
EHHHHHHHH Beautiful
It's the best, man, I mean, people
to the airport to see each other's faces, dude, it's like
eggs
Alendroide didn't subtitle this xD
How great!
How cool
Look at that gentleman
Ehhh!
eggs
(Spartan Shout :v)
(another Spartan shout :v)
Holy crap, kid.
AVALANCHE
AVALANCHE!!
WE'RE GOING TO SHIT!!!... I mean, TO KILL!!!
TU
This is dangerous, kid... Ala Ala Ala
What madness you, what madness
LOL
CRAZY, CRAZY CRAZY CRAZY CRAZY CRAZY
Crazy... Crazy... Crazy
Look at this *laughs* xd
Great Peru, great :D
Hey, they're coming from the other side.
rice, rice, rice
We'll see...
Made mía boy, Mr. President here
The fucking boss
you that but but but but
LOL
The people of Peru, I mean, I'm surprising myself, huh?
Tab
(Don't subscribe to Alendroide :v) They are arguing there
Danger :u
*Ust Re- incarnates in another body :u*
What a fucking crazy guy. They took a taxi, dude.
But here goes a whole family, man.
There is the sister, the aunt
the cousin *laughs at the blond*
DON'T TAKE OFF YOUR HELMET, YOU CRAZY FUCKING MAN
PUT IT ON >:v
That's so cool, man.
Okay, I just got to the room and... I don't know if you're hearing that there.
There are people outside, man.
Perate!
Let's try not to attract too much attention...
They are singing, uncle
Have you seen me?
They've seen me *laughs*
Can this be opened?
Let's see...
Guatafac
Then I go down
Oh my God... What is this? Who put it here?
It's the dick, like a super open place .. Spacious
I can take a bath... Naked
While I hear people shouting my name ( ͡ ͡° ͜ ʖ ͡ ͡°)
Okay then..
Peru's reception has been awesome.
I mean....
What are you singing, man?
They have speakers and everything :0
This is the sauna bath... Get in ( ͡ ͡° ͜ ʖ ͡ ͡°)
What do I do? M: Do you see the button on your right... Here?
Is this it?
Am I not going to get wet? ( ͡ ͡° ͜ ʖ ͡ ͡°)
Nonono, it falls from above... I think
That he is dying, that he is dying D:
*Laughs*
*Drug music* (?)
*More music* :v
Now...
We go down!
CEBICHEH!
GET OUT GET OUT IF YOU WANT TO GET OUT GET OUT NOW!
*Op music again*
Okay, I just got to the room and I just realized thateee
You gave me... some underwear.
I don't know why, I just hope they're not used.
I mean
I mean, look how... Messages here
OK
Rubiuh of my 00:07:43,615 how much I love you, seriously. I've sold
Cho... you compare.. Stop waaah
To pay the entrance fee for ohhh, how cool
That's a lot of nice messages from different people, man, how cool
But why in underwear? I mean, that's the only thing I don't understand.
I don't know who came up with the idea of putting this in a shower, man.
Good morning humans, how are you?
The first thing I saw today when I woke up was this.
Look at this shit men
It is supposed to be normal that here in Peru
Be like Silent Hill every day of the week or something
It's like a 24/7 horror movie bro
Let's see if there are people down here jelou uhhh
There are people, there are people, there are people :0
Good morning!
Ehhhh!
EHHHHHH!
Hey, what's that, man? Why are there kids on a rooftop?
Guatafack
Girl, be careful you'll kill yourself, be careful you'll kill yourself, because there...
There right there on your right, there's a hell of a lot of shit.
Little girl, please be careful.
Okay, okay, get out of there, you're safe there. You too, please.
Safety first :v
Carajoh
That's how it is all day :D
*Music*
Your subscribe
And give it a like if you want, subscribe to it.
Subtitles by Alendroide, Adrian Esteban Cardozo Duque and AshDrag 7